Someone has to fix the problems.
The Mechanic is a action, thriller, crime film directed by Simon West.
Arthur Bishop is a 'mechanic' - an elite assassin with a strict code
requiring professional perfection and total detachment.
One of an elite group of assassins, Bishop may be the best in the business
- with a unique talent for cleanly eliminating targets.
When Harry McKenna, his close friend and mentor, is murdered, Harry's son comes to him with vengeance in
his heart and a desire to learn Bishop's trade, signaling the birth of a deadly partnership.
Arthur Bishop, played by Jason Statham.
Steve McKenna, played by Ben Foster.
Harry McKenna, played by Donald Sutherland.
Sara, played by Mini Anden.
Dean Sanderson, played by Tony Goldwyn.
Kelly, played by Christa Campbell.
The Mechanic is a 2011 American action thriller film directed by Simon West, and
starring Jason Statham, Ben Foster, Tony Goldwyn, and Donald Sutherland.
A remake of the 1972 film of the same name, it centers on Arthur Bishop (Statham), a professional assassin or
'mechanic', who specializes in making his hits look like accidents, suicides and petty criminals' acts.
It was released in the U.S.
and Canada on January 28, 2011, where it was praised for its
action sequences and Statham's performance.
A sequel, Mechanic: Resurrection, was released on August 26, 2016.
The film explores themes of chicago, illinois,
research, martial arts, assassin, prostitute.
The tone is intense.